<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<languages>
    <language>
        <name>Afrikaans</name>
        <text>
            EK AM VEGAN
            
            Plantaardige voedsel net asseblief!
            GEEN VLEIS
            Geen soogdier, voël, vis, seekos, insekte, sous, sous daaroor ...
            GEEN EIER
            Geen blankes, albumien, dooier ...
            GEEN SUIWELPRODUKTE
            Geen melk, kaas, jogurt, wei, kaseïen, laktose ...
            GEEN DIER
            Nee heuning, gelatien, varkvet, olie, bloed, been, vet ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Albanian</name>
        <text>
            UNË JAM VEGAN
            
            Ushqimeve bimore vetëm ju lutem!
            ASNJË MISH
            Nuk ka gjitar, zog, peshk, ushqim deti, insekteve salcë, lëng mishi...
            NUK KA VEZË
            Nuk ka të bardhë, albuminë, e verdhë veze...
            NUK QUMËSHTIT
            Nuk ka qumësht, djathë, kos, hirrë, kazeinë, lactose...
            KA PRODUKTE SHTAZORE
            Nuk ka mjaltë, xhelatinë, sallo naftës, gjaku, kockave, yndyrë...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Arabic</name>
        <text>
            أنا نباتي
            
            الأغذية النباتية فقط من فضلك!
            لا لحم
            لا الثدييات والطيور والأسماك والمأكولات البحرية، والحشرات، وصلصة، مرق ...
            لا البيض
            لا تضع بياض البيض، زلال، صفار البيض ...
            لا الألبان
            لا الحليب والجبن واللبن ومصل اللبن، الكازين واللاكتوز ...
            لا توجد منتجات الحيوان
            لا العسل، والجيلاتين، وشحم الخنزير وزيت والدم والعظام والدهون ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Armenian</name>
        <text>
            ԵՍ VEGAN
            
            բուսական սնունդ, միայն խնդրում եմ.
            ոչ միս
            ոչ կաթնասուն կենդանի, թռչուն, ձուկ, ծովամթերք, միջատների, սոուս,
            արգանակ ...
            ոչ ձու
            ոչ սպիտակ գույնի շորեր, սպիտակուց, ձվի դեղնուց ...
            ոչ կաթնամթերքի
            ոչ կաթ, պանիր, մածուն, շիճուկ, կազեին, կաթնաշաքար ...
            ոչ Անասնաբուծական արտադրանքներ
            ոչ մեղր, դոնդող, համեմել, ձեթ, արյան, ոսկորների, ճարպ ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Azerbaijani</name>
        <text>
            Mən VEGAN AM
            
            Bitkisel yalnız edin!
            HEÇ BIR ƏT
            Heç bir məməli, qus, balıq, deniz, böcek, sous, bulyon ...
            HEÇ BIR YUMURTA
            Heç bir whites, zülal, yumurta sarısı ...
            HEÇ BIR SÜD
            Süd, pendir, yoqurt, zərdab, kazein, laktoza ...
            HEÇ BIR HEYVAN MƏHSULLARININ
            Bal Xeyr, jelatin, piy, yağ, qan, sümük, piy ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Basque</name>
        <text>
            VEGAN AM DUT
            
            Landare elikagai bakarrik please!
            HARAGIA EZ
            ugaztun ez, hegazti, arrain, itsaski, intsektu, saltsa, salda ...
            ARRAUTZA EZ
            zuriak ez, albumen, gorringoa ...
            ESNE EZ
            Ez esnea, gazta, jogurt, whey, casein, laktosa ...
            EZ DAGO ANIMALIA PRODUKTU
            Ez eztia, gelatina, gantzaz prestatutakoa, olioa, odol, hezur, koipe ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Belarusian</name>
        <text>
            Я СТРОГІ ВЕГЕТАРЫЯНЕЦ
            
            Расліннай ежы толькі, калі ласка!
            НЯМА МЯСА
            Няма млекакормячых, птушак, рыба, морапрадукты,
            насякомых, соус, булён ...
            НЯ ЯЙКА
            Ня вавёркі, бялок, жаўток ...
            НЯМА МАЛОЧНЫХ
            Не малако, сыр, ёгурт, сыроватка, казеін, лактоза ...
            НЯМА ПРАДУКТАЎ ЖЫВЁЛЬНАГА ПАХОДЖАННЯ
            Не мёд, жэлацін, сала, масла, кроў, косці, тлушч ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Bengali</name>
        <text>
            আমি VEGAN
            
            উদ্ভিদ খাদ্য শুধুমাত্র দয়া করে!
            কোন মাংস
            কোন স্তন্যপায়ী, পাখি, মাছ, সীফুড, পোকা, সস, জুস ...
            কোন ডিম
            কোন সাদা, শস্য, কুসুম ...
            কোন ডেইরি
            কোন দুধ, পনির, দই, মাঠা, ছানাজাতীয় উপাদান, ল্যাকটোজ ...
            কোন প্রানীজ
            মধু না, সিরিশ-আঠা, চর্বি, তেল, রক্ত, হাড়, চর্বি ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Bosnian</name>
        <text>
            JA SAM VEGAN
            
            Biljnih namirnica jedino molim!
            NEMA MESA
            Ne sisara, ptica, riba, morski plodovi, insekata, sos, bujon ...
            NO JAJE
            Nema bijelaca, bjelance, žumance ...
            NEMA MLIJEČNIH
            Ne mlijeko, sir, jogurt, surutka, kazein, laktoza ...
            NEMA ŽIVOTINJSKIH PROIZVODA
            Nema meda, želatin, mast, ulje, krv, kosti, masti ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Bulgarian</name>
        <text>
            АЗ СЪМ ВЕГАН
            
            Само с растителна храна, моля!
            НЯМА МЕСО
            Бозайници, птици, риба, морски дарове,
            насекоми, сос, бульон ...
            НЕ ЯЙЦЕ
            Не бели, белтък, жълтък ...
            НЕ МЛЕЧНИ ПРОДУКТИ
            Не е мляко, сирене, кисело мляко, суроватка, казеин, лактоза ...
            НИТО ЕДНО ЖИВОТНО ПРОДУКТИ
            Не мед, желатин, свинска мас, масло, кръв, кости, мазнини ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Cambodian (Khmer)</name>
        <text>
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Catalan</name>
        <text>
            JO SÓC VEGÀ
            
            Aliments d'origen vegetal només si us plau!
            SENSE CARN
            No mamífers, aus, peixos, mariscs, insectes, salsa, brou ...
            SENSE OU
            No blancs, albúmina, rovell d'ou ...
            NO LACTIS
            No hi ha llet, formatge, iogurt, sèrum de llet, caseïna, lactosa ...
            SENSE PRODUCTES D'ORIGEN ANIMAL
            No la mel, gelatina, mantega, oli, sang, os, greix ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Cebuano</name>
        <text>
            AKO MAO VEGAN
            
            Tanom nga pagkaon lamang please!
            WALAY BISAN UNSA NGA KALAN-ON
            Walay mga mammal, langgam, isda,
            seafood, insekto, salsahan, sabaw ...
            WALAY BISAN UNSA NGA ITLOG
            Walay mga puti, albumen, yolk ...
            WALAY BISAN UNSA NGA DAIRY
            Nga walay gatas, keso, yogurt, whey, casein, lactose ...
            NGA WALAY MGA MANANAP NGA MGA PRODUKTO
            Walay bisan unsa nga dugos, gelatin, 
            lard, sa lana, sa dugo, bukog, tambok ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Chinese (simplified)</name>
        <text>
            我是严格素食主义者：
            
            我只吃植物性食物！
            非肉类：
            不吃哺乳动物类，鸟类，鱼类，海鲜，昆虫，肉酱汁，肉汤...
            非蛋类：
            不吃蛋清，蛋白，蛋黄...
            非奶类：
            不吃牛奶，奶酪，酸奶，乳清，酪蛋白，乳糖...
            非任何其他别的动物产品：
            不吃蜂蜜，骨胶果冻，猪油，其他别的动物油，血，骨，脂肪...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Chinese (traditional)</name>
        <text>
            我是严格素食主义者：
            
            我只吃植物性食物！
            非肉类：
            不吃哺乳动物类，鸟类，鱼类，海鲜，昆虫，肉酱汁，肉汤...
            非蛋类：
            不吃蛋清，蛋白，蛋黄...
            非奶类：
            不吃牛奶，奶酪，酸奶，乳清，酪蛋白，乳糖...
            非任何其他别的动物产品：
            不吃蜂蜜，骨胶果冻，猪油，其他别的动物油，血，骨，脂肪...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Croatian</name>
        <text>
            JA SAM VEGAN
            
            Biljne hrane samo molim!
            BEZ MESA
            Nema sisavaca, ptica, riba, plodovi mora,
            insekata, umak, juhu ...
            BEZ JAJA
            Ne bijele, bjelanjak, žumanjak ...
            NEMA MLIJEKA
            Ne mlijeko, sir, jogurt, sirutka, kazein, laktoza ...
            BEZ ŽIVOTINJSKIH PROIZVODA
            Nema meda, želatina, svinjska mast, ulje, krv, kosti, masnoće ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Czech</name>
        <text>
            JSEM VEGAN
            
            Pouze rostlinné potraviny, prosím!
            ŽÁDNÉ MASO
            Žádné savec, pták, ryba, mořské plody, hmyz, omáčky, vývar ...
            ŽÁDNÉ VEJCE
            Ne bílé, bílek, žloutek ...
            BEZ MLÉKA A MLÉČNÝCH VÝROBKŮ
            Žádné mléko, sýr, jogurt, syrovátka, kasein, laktóza ...
            ŽÁDNÉ ŽIVOČIŠNÉ PRODUKTY
            Žádný med, želatinu, sádlo, olej, krev, kosti, tuk ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Danish</name>
        <text>
            JEG ER VEGANER
            
            Kun planteføde tak!
            INTET KØD
            Ingen pattedyr, fugle, fisk, skaldyr, insekter, sauce, bouillon ...
            INGEN ÆG
            Ingen æggehvide, æggehvidestof, blomme ...
            INGEN MEJERIPRODUKTER
            Ingen mælk, ost, yoghurt, valle, kasein, lactose ...
            INGEN DYREPRODUKTER
            Ingen honning, gelatine, svinefedt, olie, blod, knogler, fedt ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Dutch</name>
        <text>
            IK BEN VEGAN
            
            Alleen plantaardige voedsel, alstublieft!
            GEEN VLEES
            Geen zoogdier, vogel, vis, zeevruchten, insect, saus, bouillon
            GEEN EIEREN
            Geen eiwitten, eierdooier...
            GEEN ZUIVEL
            Geen melk, kaas, yoghurt, wei, caseïne, lactose ...
            GEEN DIERLIJKE PRODUCTEN
            Geen honing, gelatine, reuzel, olie, bloed, bot, vet ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>English</name>
        <text>
            I AM VEGAN
            
            Plant foods only please!
            NO MEAT
            No mammal, bird, fish, seafood, insect, sauce, broth...
            NO EGG
            No whites, albumen, yolk...
            NO DAIRY
            No milk, cheese, yogurt, whey, casein, lactose...
            NO ANIMAL PRODUCTS
            No honey, gelatin, lard, oil, blood, bone, fat...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Esperanto</name>
        <text>
            MI ESTAS VEGANA
            
            Planto nutraĵojn nur bonvolu!
            NENIU KARNO
            Neniu mamulo, birdo, fiŝo, mariskoj, insekto, saŭco, buljono ...
            NENIU OVO
            Neniu blankuloj, albumino, yema ...
            NENIU LAKTO
            Neniu lakto, fromaĝo, jogurto, serumo, kazeino, laktozo ...
            NENIU BESTO PRODUKTOJ
            Neniu mielo, gelateno, lardo, oleo, sango, osto, graso ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Estonian</name>
        <text>
            MA OLEN VEGAN
            
            Taimetoiduküllane ainult palun!
            ILMA LIHATA
            Ei imetaja, lind, kala, mereande, putukate, kaste, puljong ...
            ÜHTEGI MUNA
            Ei ole valged, albumiin, munakollane ...
            EI MEIEREI
            Ei piim, juust, jogurt, vadak, kaseiin, laktoos ...
            EI OLE LOOMSETE SAADUSTE
            Ei ole mesi, želatiin, sulatatud searasva õli, veri, luud, rasva ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Filipino</name>
        <text>
            AKO VEGAN
            
            Pagkaing halaman lamang mangyaring!
            WALANG KARNE
            Walang mga hayop na nagpapasuso, ibon, isda, seafood, insekto, sarsa, sabaw ...
            WALANG ITLOG
            Walang mga puti, puti ng itlog, yok ...
            WALANG PAGAWAAN NG GATAS
            Walang gatas, keso, yogurt, patis ng gatas, kasein, lactose ...
            WALANG HAYOP MGA PRODUKTO
            Walang honey, gulaman, mantika, langis, dugo, buto, taba ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Finnish</name>
        <text>
            OLEN VEGAANI
            
            Kasvisruokaa vain kiitos!
            EI LIHAA
            Ei nisäkäs, lintu, kala, äyriäiset, hyönteiset, kastike, lihaliemi ...
            EI MUNA
            Ei valkoiset, valkuaisen, keltuainen ...
            EI MAITOA
            Ei maitoa, juustoa, jogurtti, hera, kaseiini, laktoosi ...
            EI ELÄINTUOTTEET
            Ei hunajaa, liivatetta, laardi, öljy, veri, luu, rasvan ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>French</name>
        <text>
            JE SUIS VEGAN
            
            Aliments d'origine végétale seulement s'il vous plaît!
            PAS DE VIANDE
            Pas de mammifères, d'oiseaux, poissons, crustacés, d'insectes, de la sauce, bouillon ...
            SANS OEUF
            Pas les Blancs, l'albumine, le jaune ...
            SANS PRODUITS LAITIERS
            Pas de lait, fromage, yogourt, lait, la caséine, le lactose ...
            PAS DE PRODUITS ANIMAUX
            Pas de miel, de la gélatine, saindoux, huile, sang, os, graisse ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Galician</name>
        <text>
            EU SON VEGAN
            
            Alimentos de orixe vexetal só por favor!
            SEN CARNE
            Non mamíferos, aves, peixes, mariscos, insectos, salsa de caldo de carne, ...
            NINGÚN OVO
            Non brancos, albúmen, xema ...
            NINGUNHA LEITE
            Sen leite, queixo, iogur, soro de leite, a caseína, lactosa ...
            SEN PRODUTOS ANIMAIS
            Ningún mel, gelatina, baña, aceite, sangue, ósos, graxa ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Georgian</name>
        <text>
            მე VEGAN
            
            მცენარეული საკვები მხოლოდ გთხოვთ!
            არ ხორცი
            არ mammal, ფრინველი, თევზი, ზღვის პროდუქტები, მწერების, სოუსი, ბულიონი ...
            არ კვერცხი
            არ თეთრკანიანი, albumen, yolk ...
            არ რძის
            არ რძე, ყველი, იოგურტი, ჭიქურა, casein, ლაქტოზის ...
            არ მეცხოველეობის პროდუქციის
            არ თაფლი, ჟელატინი, lard, ზეთი, სისხლის, ძვლის, ცხიმის ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>German</name>
        <text>
            ICH BIN VEGAN
            
            Bitte, nur pflanzliches Essen!
            KEIN FLEISCH
            Kein/e Säugetier, Vogel, Fisch, Meeresfrüchte, Insekt, Soße, Brühe …
            KEINE EIER
            Keine Eiweiße, Eiklar, Eigelbe ...
            KEINE MILCHPRODUKTE
            Kein/e Milch, Käse, Joghurt, Molke, Kasein, Laktose ...
            KEINE TIERISCHEN PRODUKTE
            Kein/e Honig, Gelatine, Schmalz, Öl, Blut, Knochen, Fett ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Greek</name>
        <text>
            ΕΙΜΑΙ VEGAN
            
            Φυτικές τροφές μόνο παρακαλώ!
            ΟΧΙ ΚΡΕΑΣ
            Δεν θηλαστικών, πουλιών, τα ψάρια, τα θαλασσινά, τα έντομα, σάλτσα, ζωμό ...
            ΟΧΙ ΑΥΓΟ
            Δεν υπάρχουν λευκοί, ασπράδι αυγού, κρόκος ...
            ΟΧΙ ΓΑΛΑΚΤΟΚΟΜΙΚΑ
            Δεν γάλα, τυρί, γιαούρτι, ορός γάλακτος, καζεΐνη, λακτόζη ...
            Καθόλου ζωικά προϊόντα
            Δεν μέλι, ζελατίνη, λαρδί, έλαιο, αίμα, οστά, λίπος ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Guajarati</name>
        <text>
            હું વેગન છું
            
            છોડ ખોરાક માત્ર કૃપા કરીને!
            આ બોલ પર કોઈ મીટ
            આ બોલ પર કોઈ સસ્તન, પક્ષી, માછલી, સીફૂડ, જંતુ, સોસ, સૂપ ...
            આ બોલ પર કોઈ એગ
            આ બોલ પર કોઈ ગોરા, ઈંડાની સફેદી, જરદી ...
            આ બોલ પર કોઈ ડેરી
            આ બોલ પર કોઈ દૂધ, ચીઝ, દહીં, છાશ, પનીરનું પ્રોટીન દ્રવ્ય, લેક્ટોઝ ...
            આ બોલ પર કોઈ પશુ પ્રોડક્ટ્સ
            મધ ના, જિલેટીન, ચરબીયુક્ત, તેલ, લોહી, અસ્થિ, ચરબી ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Haitian Creole</name>
        <text>
            SE MWEN MENM VEGAN
            
            Manje plant sèlman tanpri!
            PA GEN OKENN VYANN
            Pa gen okenn mamifè, zwazo, pwason, bèt lanmè, ensèk, sòs, bouyon…
            PA GEN OKENN ZE
            Pa gen okenn blan, albumine, jònze ...
            PA GEN OKENN LETYE
            Pa gen okenn lèt, fwomaj, yogout, laktoserom, kazein, laktoz ...
            PA GEN OKENN PWODWI BÈT
            Pa gen okenn siwo myèl, jelatin, lwil là kochon, san, nan zo, grès ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Hebrew</name>
        <text>
            אני טבעוני
            
            מזונות צמחיים בלבד בבקשה!
            אין בשר
            אין יונק, ציפור, דגים, פירות ים, חרקים, רוטב, מרק ...
            לא ביצה
            ללא חלבונים, חלבון, חלמון ...
            לא חלב
            אין חלב, גבינה, יוגורט, גבינה, קזאין, לקטוז ...
            אין מוצרים מן החי
            לא דבש, ג'לטין, שומן, שמן, דם, עצמות, שומן ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Hindi</name>
        <text>
            मैं शाकाहारी हूँ
            
            संयंत्र खाद्य पदार्थ केवल कृपया!
            कोई मांस
            कोई स्तनपायी, पक्षी, मछली, समुद्री भोजन, कीट, सॉस, शोरबा ...
            कोई अंडा
            कोई सफेद, अंडे की सफ़ेदी, जर्दी ...
            कोई डेयरी
            कोई दूध, पनीर, दही, मट्ठा, कैसिइन, लैक्टोज ...
            कोई पशु उत्पाद
            शहद नहीं, जिलेटिन, चिकना, तेल, रक्त, हड्डी, वसा ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Hmong</name>
        <text>
            KUV YOG NEEG TSIS NOJ NQAIJ
            
            Nroj cov khoom noj uas tsuas thov!
            TSIS MUAJ NQAIJ
            Tsis muaj mammal, noog, ntses,
            nqaij hav dej, kab, sauce, broth ...
            TSIS MUAJ QE
            Tsis dawb, albumen, yolk ...
            TSIS MUAJ CHAW YUJ NYUJ
            Tsis muaj mis nyuj, cheese, yogurt, whey, casein, lactose ...
            TSIS MUAJ TSIAJ COV KHOOM
            Tsis muaj zib mu, gelatin, lard, roj, 
            ntshav, cov pob txha, muaj roj ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Hungarian</name>
        <text>
            ÉN VEGÁN
            
            Növényi élelmiszerek csak kérem!
            NINCS HÚS
            Nem emlıs, madár, hal, tenger gyümölcsei, rovar, mártás, leves ...
            NEM TOJÁS
            Nem fehérek, albumin, tojássárgája ...
            NEM TEJTERMÉKEK
            Nincs tej, sajt, joghurt, tejsavó, kazein, laktóz ...
            NEM ÁLLATI EREDETŐ TERMÉKEK
            Nincs méz, zselatin, zsír-, olaj-, vér-, csont-, zsír ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Icelandic</name>
        <text>
            ÉG ER VEGAN
            
            Planta matvæli vinsamlegast bara!
            EKKI KJÖT
            Engin spendýra, fugla, fiska, sjávarfang, skordýrum, sósa, seyði ...
            ENGIN EGG
            Ekki hvítur, albumen, eggjarauða ...
            ENGAR MJÓLKURVÖRUR
            Engin mjólk, ostur, jógúrt, mysa, kasín, laktósi ...
            EKKI DÝRAAFURÐIR
            Ekki hunang, gelatín, lard, olíu, blóð, bein, fitu ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Indonesian</name>
        <text>
            SAYA VEGAN
            
            Makanan nabati only please!
            TANPA DAGING
            Tidak ada mamalia, burung, ikan, makanan laut, serangga, saus, kaldu
            TELUR TIDAK ADA
            Tidak ada putih, albumen, kuning telur ...
            SUSU TIDAK ADA
            Tidak ada susu, keju, yoghurt, whey, kasein, laktosa ...
            TANPA PRODUK HEWANI
            Tidak ada madu, gelatin, lemak, minyak, darah, tulang, lemak ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Irish</name>
        <text>
            TÁ MÉ VEGAN
            
            Bianna gléasra ach amháin le do thoil!
            AON FHEOIL
            Aon mamach, éan, iasc, bia mara, feithidí, anlann, brat ...
            AON UBH
            Aon whites, albumen, buíocán ...
            AON DÉIRÍOCHTA
            Aon bainne, cáis, iógart, meadhg, cáiséin, lachtós ...
            THÁIRGÍ AINMHITHE NACH
            Aon mil, geilitín, blonag, ola, fuil, cnámh, saill ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Italian</name>
        <text>
            IO SONO VEGANO / A
            
            Solo alimenti vegetali per favore!
            NIENTE CARNE
            Niente mammiferi, uccelli, pesci, crostacei, insetti, sughi di carne, brodi di carne...
            NIENTE UOVA
            Niente albume, tuorlo...
            NIENTE LATTICINI
            Niente latte, formaggio, yogurt, siero di latte, caseina, lattosio...
            NIENTE PRODOTTI ANIMALI
            Niente miele, gelatina, strutto, olio animale, sangue, ossa, grasso...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Japanese</name>
        <text>
            私はビーガンです
            
            植物性食品のみでお願い！
            ない肉なし
            は哺乳類ない、鳥、魚、魚介類、昆虫、醤油、ブイヨン...
            は卵なし
            ない白人ない、卵白、卵黄...
            は乳製品なし
            は牛乳、チーズない、ヨーグルト、乳清、カゼイン、乳糖...
            何の動物製品なし
            蜂蜜がない、ゼラチン、ラード、油、血液、骨、脂肪...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Javanese</name>
        <text>
            AKU VEGAN
            
            Tetanduran panganan mung please!
            ORA MEAT
            Ora mammal, manuk, iwak, panganan laut,
            serangga, sauce, duduh kaldu ...
            ORA ENDHOG
            Ora tiyang kuilt pethak, albumen, yolk ...
            ORA BIASA
            Ora susu, keju, yogurt, whey, casein, lactose ...
            ORA PRODUK KEWAN
            Ora madu, gelatin, lard, lenga, getih, balung, lemak ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Kannada</name>
        <text>
            ನಾನು ವೆಗನ್ am
            
            ಸಸ್ಯಾಹಾರ ಮಾತ್ರ ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು!
            ಯಾವುದೇ ಮಾಂಸ
            ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಸ್ತನಿ, ಪಕ್ಷಿ, ಮೀನು, ಕಡಲ, ಕೀಟ, ಸಾಸ್, ಮಾಂಸದ ಸಾರು ...
            ಇಲ್ಲ ಎಗ್
            ಇಲ್ಲ ಬಿಳಿಯರು, ಅಂಡಶ್ವೇತ, ಹಳದಿ ...
            ಯಾವುದೇ ಡೈರಿ
            ಯಾವುದೇ ಹಾಲು, ಬೆಣ್ಣೆ, ಮೊಸರು, ಹಾಲೊಡಕು, ಕ್ಯಾಸೀಯ್ನ್ ಎಂಬುದು, ಲ್ಯಾಕ್ಟೋಸ್ ...
            ಯಾವುದೇ ಪ್ರಾಣಿ ಉತ್ಪನ್ನಗಳು
            ಜೇನು ಇಲ್ಲ, ಜೆಲಾಟಿನ್, ತುಪ್ಪ, ಎಣ್ಣೆ, ರಕ್ತ, ಮೂಳೆ, ಕೊಬ್ಬು ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Korean</name>
        <text>
            나는 식물이다
            
            공장 식품은 제발!
            아무 고기도
            어떤 포유류도 조류, 생선, 해산물, 곤충, 소스, 수프 ...
            아무 계란도
            도 백인도 횐자위, 노른자 ...
            유제품
            더 우유, 치즈도, 요구르트, 유청, 카제인, 유당 ...
            어떤 동물 제품 없음
            꿀 아니, 젤라틴, 라드, 기름, 혈액, 뼈, 지방 ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Lao</name>
        <text>
            ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າແມ່ນຜັກ
            
            ອາຫານທີ່ພືດເທົ່ານັ້ນກະລຸນາ!
            ຊີ້ນບໍ່ມີ
            mammal ບໍ່ມີ, ນົກ, ປາ, ອາຫານທະເລ, ແມງໄມ້, ຍັງ, broth ...
            ໄຂ່ທີ່ບໍ່ມີ
            ສີຂາວທີ່ບໍ່ມີ, ໄຂ່ຂາວ, yolk ...
            ນົມບໍ່ມີ
            ບໍ່ມີນົມເນີຍແຂງ,, ນົມສົ້ມ, whey, casein, lactose ...
            ບໍ່ມີຜະລິດຕະພັນສັດ
            ບໍ່ມີການ້ໍາເຜີ້ງ, gelatin, ນໍ້າມັນ, ນ້ໍາ, ເລືອດ, ກະດູກ, ໄຂມັນ ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Latin</name>
        <text>
            EGO VEGAN
            
            Donec venenatis pretium nisi!
            CARNEM NON
            Animal nulla, et volucrum, piscium seafood, insecto diam, jus ...
            NON OVUM
            Nulla whites, albumen, vitellus ...
            NULLA DAIRY
            Non lac, caseus, yogurt, sero, casein, lactose ...
            NULLUM ANIMAL NISI
            No mel, gelatina, lardum, oleum, sanguis, rhoncus, pingues ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Latvian</name>
        <text>
            ES ESMU VEG NS
            
            Augu pārtikas produkti, tikai, lūdzu!
            BEZ GAěAS
            Nav zīdītāju, putnu, zivju, jūras veltes, kukainis, mērci, buljonu ...
            NAV OLU
            Nē baltumus, olbaltumvielas, olas dzeltenums ...
            NE PIENA
            Nav piens, siers, jogurts, sūkalas, kazeīns, laktozes ...
            NAV DZĪVNIEKU IZCELSMES PRODUKTI
            Bez medus, želatīns, cūku tauki, eĜĜas, asins, kaulu, tauku ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Lithuanian</name>
        <text>
            AŠ ESU veganų
            
            Augalų maisto tik prašom!
            be mėsos
            Nėra žinduolių, paukščių, žuvų, jūros gėrybių, vabzdžių, padažas, sultinys ...
            NE KIAUŠINIŲ
            Nėra baltymai, baltymai, tryniai ...
            NE PIENO
            Ne pienas, sūris, jogurtas, išrūgų, kazeino, laktozės ...
            Joks gyvūnas PRODUKTAI
            Ne medus, želatina, taukai, aliejus, kraujo, kaulų, riebalų ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Macedonian</name>
        <text>
            ЈАС СУМ ВЕГАН
            
            Растителната храна само ве молам!
            НЕ МЕСО
            Не цицачи, птици, риба, морски плодови, инсекти, сос, супа
            НЕ ЈАЈЦЕ
            Не белците, albumen, жолчка ...
            НЕ МЛЕЧНИ
            Не млеко, сирење, јогурт, сурутка, казеин, лактоза ...
            НЕ ПРОИЗВОДИ ОД ЖИВОТИНСКО ПОТЕКЛО
            Не мед, желатин, маст, масло, крв, коски, масти ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Malay</name>
        <text>
            SAYA PM VEGAN
            
            Makanan tumbuhan sahaja sila!
            DAGING TIDAK
            Tiada mamalia, burung, ikan, makanan laut, serangga, sos, sup
            TELUR TIDAK
            Tiada putih, albumen, kuning telur ...
            TENUSU TIDAK
            Tiada susu, keju, yogurt, whey, kasein, laktosa ...
            TIADA HAIWAN PRODUK
            Tiada madu, gelatin, lemak, minyak, darah, tulang, lemak ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Maltese</name>
        <text>
            JIENA VEGAN
            
            Ikel tal-pjanti biss jekk jogħġbok!
            EBDA LAĦAM
            Ebda mammiferu, għasafar, ħut, frott tal-baħar, insetti, zalza, brodu ...
            EBDA BAJD
            Ebda abjad, albumina, isfar ...
            EBDA TAL-ĦALIB
            Nru tal-ħalib, ġobon, jogurt, xorrox, kaseina, lattosju ...
            EBDA PRODOTTI TAL-ANNIMALI
            Ebda għasel, ġelatina, xaħam, żejt, demm, għadam, xaħam ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Marathi</name>
        <text>
            मी प्राण्यापासून तयार झालेले काहीही am
            
            वनस्पती अन्न केवळ करा!
            नाही मांस
            नाही सस्तन प्राणी, पक्षी, मासे, सीफुड, किटक, सॉस, मटनाचा रस्सा ...
            नाही अंडे
            नाही पंचा, अंड्यातील पांढरा बलक, अंड्यातील पिवळ बलक ...
            नाही दुग्धशाळा
            नाही दूध, चीज, दही, दह्यातील पाणी (विरजणातील दह्याची निवळी), दुधातील सत्त्वमय, दुग्धशर्करा ...
            कोणतेही प्राणी उत्पादने
            मध नाही, सरस, स्वयंपाकात वापरण्याची डुकराची चरबी, तेल, रक्त, अस्थी, चरबी ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Mongolian</name>
        <text>
            БИ ВЕГАН ХООЛТОН
            
            Зөвхөн ургамлан хоол хүсье!
            МАХ ОРОХГҮЙ
            Сүүн тэжээлт амьтад, шувуу, загас, далайн амьтад, шавьж,
            аливаа амьтны гаралтай соус, шөл... орохгүй
            ӨНДӨГ ОРОХГҮЙ
            Өндөгний цагаан, уураг, шар... орохгүй
            ЦАГААН ИДЭЭ ОРОХГҮЙ
            Сүү, тараг, шар ус, сүүний сахар, казейн... орохгүй
            АМЬТНЫ ГАРАЛТАЙ БҮТЭЭГДЭХҮҮНҮҮД ОРОХГҮЙ
            Зөгийн бал, амьтны цэлцгий, тос, цус, яс, өөх тос зэрэг орохгүй
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Norwegian</name>
        <text>
            JEG ER VEGANSK
            
            Plant mat bare please!
            NO KJØTT
            Ingen pattedyr, fugl, fisk, sjømat, insekt, saus, buljong ...
            INGEN EGG
            Ingen hvite, albumen, eggeplomme ...
            INGEN MEIERIPRODUKTER
            Ingen melk, ost, yoghurt, myse, kasein, laktose ...
            INGEN ANIMALSKE PRODUKTER
            Ingen honning, gelatin, smult, olje, blod, bein, fett ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Persian</name>
        <text>
            من وگان هستم
            
            غذاهای گیاهی فقط لطفا!
            بدون گوشت
            بدون پستاندار، پرنده، ماهی، غذاهای دریایی، حشرات، سس، آبگوشت ...
            هیچ تخم مرغ
            بدون سفیده، سفیده تخم مرغ، زرده ...
            هیچ فراورده های لبنی
            بدون شیر، پنیر، ماست، کشک، کازئین، لاکتوز ...
            بدون محصولات حیوانی
            عسل، ژلاتین، گوشت خوک، روغن، خون، استخوان، چربی ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Polish</name>
        <text>
            JESTEM WEGANINEM
            
            Produkty roślinne tylko proszę!
            BEZ MIĘSA
            Żaden ssak, ptak, ryby, owoce morza, owadów, sos, bulion ...
            BEZ JAJ
            Nie białka, białko, żółtko ...
            NIE MLECZNA
            Nie mleko, ser, jogurt, serwatka, kazeina, laktoza ...
            NIE PRODUKTÓW ZWIERZĄT
            Nie kochanie, żelatyna, smalec, olej, krew, kości, tłuszcz ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Portuguese</name>
        <text>
            EU SOU VEGANO / A
            
            Alimentos de plantas somente, por favor!
            SEM CARNE
            Sem mamíferos, aves, peixes, frutos do mar, insetos, molho ou caldo deles...
            SEM OVO
            Sem clara, albumina, gema...
            SEM LACTICÍNIOS
            Sem leite, queijo, iogurte, soro do leite, caseína, lactose...
            SEM PRODUTOS ANIMAIS
            Sem mel, gelatina, banha, óleo, sangue, osso, gordura...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Romanian</name>
        <text>
            EU SUNT VEGAN
            
            Alimentele vegetale vă rog numai!
            FARA CARNE
            Nici un mamifer, pasăre, peste, fructe de mare, insecte, sos, supa ...
            NICI UN OU
            Nu albi, albumina, gălbenus ...
            NU LACTATE
            Nu lapte, brânză, iaurt, zer, cazeina, lactoză ...
            NICI UN ANIMAL NU PRODUSE
            Nici miere, gelatină, untură, ulei, sânge, oase, grăsime ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Russian</name>
        <text>
            Я СТРОГИЙ ВЕГЕТАРИАНЕЦ
            
            Продукты растительного происхождения только, пожалуйста!
            НЕТ МЯСА
            Нет млекопитающих, птиц, рыбы, морепродуктов, насекомых, соус, бульон…
            НЕТ ЯИЦ
            Нет белки, белок, желток ...
            НЕТ МОЛОЧНЫЙ
            Не молоко, сыр, йогурт, сыворотка, казеин, лактоза ...
            НИ ОДНО ЖИВОТНОЕ НЕ ТОВАРЫ
            Не мед, желатин, сало, масло, кровь, кости, жир ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Serbian</name>
        <text>
            ЈА САМ ВЕГАН
            
            Биљна храна само молим те!
            БЕЗ МЕСА
            Нема сисара, птица, риба, плодови мора, инсеката, сос, супа
            БЕЗ ЈАЈА
            Нема белаца, беланчевине, жуманце ...
            НЕМА МЛЕЧНИХ ПРОИЗВОДА
            Без млека, сир, јогурт, сурутка, казеин, лактоза ...
            БЕЗ ПРОИЗВОДА ЖИВОТИЊСКОГ ПОРЕКЛА
            Нема меда, желатин, маст, уље, крв, кости, маст ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Slovak</name>
        <text>
            SOM VEGAN
            
            Iba rastlinné potraviny, prosím!
            ŽIADNE MÄSO
            Žiadne cicavec, vták, ryba, morské plody, hmyz, omáčky, vývar
            ŽIADNE VAJCIA
            Nie biele, bielok, žĺtok ...
            BEZ MLIEKA A MLIEČNYCH VÝROBKOV
            Žiadne mlieko, syr, jogurt, srvátka, kazeín, laktóza ...
            ŽIADNE ŽIVOČÍŠNE PRODUKTY
            Žiadny med, želatínu, masť, olej, krv, kosti, tuk ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Slovenian</name>
        <text>
            JAZ SEM VEGAN
            
            Samo hrano rastlinskega izvora, prosim!
            BREZ MESA
            Brez sesalcev, ptic, rib, morskih sadežev, žuželk, omake, juhe ...
            BREZ JAJC
            Brez jajčnega beljaka, rumenjaka ...
            BREZ MLEKA IN MLEČNIH IZDELKOV
            Brez mleka, sira, jogurta, sirotke, kazeina, laktoze ...
            BREZ ŽIVALSKIH PROIZVODOV
            Brez medu, želatine, svinjske masti, olja, krvi, kosti, maščobe ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Spanish</name>
        <text>
            YO SOY VEGANO / A
            
            Sólo alimentos de origen vegetal por favor!
            SIN CARNE
            Sin mamíferos, aves, pescados, mariscos, insectos, salsa, caldo
            SIN HUEVO
            Sin clara de huevo, albúmina, yema de huevo ...
            SIN LÁCTEOS
            Sin leche, queso, yogur, suero de leche, caseína, lactosa ...
            SIN PRODUCTOS DE ORIGEN ANIMAL
            Sin miel, gelatina, manteca, aceite, sangre, hueso, grasa ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Swahili</name>
        <text>
            MIMI NI VEGAN
            
            Kupanda vyakula tu tafadhali!
            HAKUNA NYAMA
            Hakuna wanyama, ndege, samaki, dagaa, wadudu, mchuzi, mchuzi wa
            HAKUNA YAI
            Hakuna wazungu, albumen, yolk ...
            HAKUNA MAZIWA
            Hakuna maziwa, jibini, mtindi, maziwa, kasini, lactose ...
            BIDHAA ZA WANYAMA HAKUNA
            Hakuna asali, gelatin, mafufa ya nguruwe, mafuta, damu, mifupa, mafuta ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Swedish</name>
        <text>
            JAG ÄR VEGAN
            
            Endast mat från växter, tack!
            INGET KÖTT
            Inga däggdjur, fåglar, fisk eller annan havsmat, insekter, såser, buljong...
            INGET ÄGG
            Ingen äggvita eller äggula...
            INGA MJÖLKPRODUKTER
            Ingen mjölk, ost, yogurt, vassla, kasein, laktos...
            INGA PRODUKTER FRÅN DJUR
            Ingen honung, gelatin, ister, olja, blod, ben, fett...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Tamil</name>
        <text>
            நான் சைவ உணவு பழக்கம் தான்
            
            தாவர உணவுகளில் மட்டுமே தயவுசெய்து!
            எந்த இறைச்சி
            எந்த பாலூட்டி, பறவை, மீன், கடல் உணவுகள், பூச்சி, சாஸ், குழம்பு ...
            எந்த முட்டை
            எந்த வெள்ளை, வெள்ளை கருவுணவு, மஞ்சள் கரு ...
            எந்த பால் பண்ணை
            பால், சீஸ், தயிர், மோர், கேசீன், லாக்டோஸ் ...
            எந்த விலங்கு
            தேன் இல்லை, ஜெலட்டின், பன்றி கொழுப்பு, எண்ணெய், இரத்தம், எலும்பு, கொழுப்பு ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Teluga</name>
        <text>
            నేను వేగన్ రెడీ
            
            మొక్క ఆహారాలు మాత్రమే దయచేసి!
            సంఖ్య మీట్
            సంఖ్య క్షీరదం పక్షి, చేప, మత్స్య, కీటకాలు, సాస్, ఉడకబెట్టిన పులుసు ...
            సంఖ్య ఎగ్
            సంఖ్య శ్వేతజాతీయులు, తెల్లసొన, పచ్చసొన ...
            సంఖ్య డైరీ
            సంఖ్య పాలు, చీజ్, పెరుగు, పాలవిరుగుడు, కేస్ఇన్, లాక్టోజ్ ...
            సంఖ్య జంతు ఉత్పత్తులు
            తేనె సంఖ్య, జెలటిన్, పంది క్రోవ్వు, చమురు, రక్తం, ఎముక, కొవ్వు ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Thai</name>
        <text>
            ฉันมังสวิรัติ
            
            อาหารจากพืชเท่านั้น!
            เนื้อสัตว์ไม่มี
            เลี้ยงลูกด้วยนมไม่มีนกปลาอาหารทะเล, แมลง, ซอส, ซุป ...
            ไม่มีไข่
            ขาวไม่มีไข่ขาวไข่แดง ...
            นมไม่มี
            ไม่มีนมชีสโยเกิร์ตเวย์โปรตีนเคซีน, แลคโตส ...
            ไม่มีผลิตภัณฑ์จากสัตว์
            ไม่มีน้ำผึ้งเจลาติน, น้ำมันหมูน้ำมันเลือดกระดูกไขมัน ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Turkish</name>
        <text>
            BEN VEGAN
            
            Sadece bitkisel besinlerde lütfen!
            YOK ET
            Memeli, kus, balık, deniz ürünleri, böcek, sos, et suyu ...
            HIÇ YUMURTA
            Beyazlar, akı, yumurta sarısı ...
            HIÇ SÜT
            Süt, peynir, yoğurt, peynir altı suyu, kazein, laktoz ...
            HIÇBIR HAYVANSAL ÜRÜNLER
            Bal yok, jelatin, domuz yağı, yağ, kan, kemik, yağ ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Ukrainian</name>
        <text>
            Я СТРОГИЙ ВЕГЕТАРІАНЕЦЬ
            
            Рослинної їжі тільки, будь ласка!
            НЕМАЄ М'ЯСА
            Немає ссавців, птахів, риба, морепродукти, комах, соус, бульйон ...
            НЕ ЯЙЦЕ
            Не білки, білок, жовток ...
            НЕМАЄ МОЛОЧНИХ
            Не молоко, сир, йогурт, сироватка, казеїн, лактоза ...
            НЕМАЄ ПРОДУКТІВ ТВАРИННОГО ПОХОДЖЕННЯ
            Не мед, желатин, сало, масло, кров, кістки, жир ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Urdu</name>
        <text>
            میں Vegan ہوں
            
            پلانٹ کھانے کی اشیاء صرف براہ مہربانی!
            نہ گوشت
            کوئی ستنپایی، پرندوں، مچھلی، سمندری غذا، کیڑے، چٹنی، شوربے ...
            کوئی انڈے
            کوئی سفید، انڈے کی سفیدی، جردی ...
            کوئی ڈیری
            کوئی دودھ، پنیر، دہی، چھینے، casein، لیکٹوج ...
            کوئی جانوروں کی مصنوعات
            شہد نہیں، جلیٹن، سور کی چربی، تیل، خون، ہڈی، چربی ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Vietnamese</name>
        <text>
            TÔI ĂN THUÂN CHAY
            
            Thức ăn thực vật chỉ xin vui lòng!
            KHÔNG CÓ THỊT
            Không có động vật có vú, chim, cá, hải sản, côn trùng, nước chấm, nước dùng ...
            không trứng
            Không có người da trắng, lòng trắng, lòng đỏ ...
            KHÔNG SỮA
            Không có sữa, pho mát, sữa chua, váng sữa, casein, lactose ...
            Không có sản phẩm động vật
            Không có mật ong, gelatin, mỡ, dầu, máu, xương, mỡ ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Welsh</name>
        <text>
            YR WYF YN FEGAN
            
            Bwydydd planhigion yn unig os gwelwch yn dda!
            DIM CIG
            Dim mamaliaid, adar, pysgod, bwyd môr, pryfed, saws, cawl ...
            DIM WY
            Unrhyw gwyn, albumen, melynwy ...
            DIM LLAETH
            Dim llaeth, caws, iogwrt, maidd, gasein, lactos ...
            UNRHYW GYNNYRCH ANIFEILIAID
            Dim mêl, gelatin, lard, olew, gwaed, esgyrn, braster ...
        </text>
    </language>
    <language>
        <name>Yiddish</name>
        <text>
            איך בין וועגאַן
            
            פּלאַנט פודז נאָר ביטע!
            ניט קיין פלייש
            ניט מאַמאַל, פויגל, פיש, סעאַפאָאָד, ינסעקט, סאָוס, יויך ...
            ניט עג
            ניט קיין ווייץ, אַלבומען, יאָוק ...
            ניט מילכיק
            ניט קיין מילך, קעז, יאָגורט, וויי, קייסין, לאַקטאָוס ...
            ניט אַנימאַל פּראָדוקטן
            קיין האָניק, דזשעלאַטאַן, לאַרד, בוימל, בלוט, ביין, פעט ...
        </text>
    </language>
    
</languages>